"Lost To You"
"ضائع بالنسبة لك"
(Episode 2)
(الحلقة 2)
The rain will stop.
سيتوقف المطر.
But some marks, once they're made,
لكن بعض العلامات، بمجرد أن تُرسَم،
can never be erased.
لا يمكن محوها أبداً.
Oh my god.
يا إلهي.
He's first in our grade again.
إنه الأول في صفنا مرة أخرى.
How many times is that now?
كم مرة حدث ذلك الآن؟
Top student.
الطالب المتفوق.
So handsome.
وسيم جداً.
Single-parent family.
أسرة ذات عائل واحد.
The tragic hero.
البطل التراجيدي.
We're not on the list again.
لم نعد مدرجين في القائمة مرة أخرى.
Let's go, let's go.
هيا بنا، هيا بنا.
Zhan Wang. Zhan Wang.
زان وانغ. زان وانغ.
Yesterday, he said he'd be friends with Xu Yuan.
قال أمس إنه سيكون صديقاً لشو يوان.
And now he dares to sit with the Jinx.
والآن يجرؤ على الجلوس مع النحس.
Good grades, huh?
درجات جيدة، أليس كذلك؟
That's hilarious.
هذا مضحك للغاية.
Hilarious, right?
مضحك للغاية، أليس كذلك؟
What a waste of a handsome face.
يا له من إهدار لوجه وسيم.
The power of that Jinx...
قوة تلك اللعنة...
is no joke.
الأمر ليس مزحة.
Just you wait.
انتظر فقط.
He's in for some serious bad luck.
سيواجه بعض الحظ السيئ للغاية.
Let's make a deal.
لنعقد صفقة.
Give me back my grandma's house.
أعيدوا لي منزل جدتي.
I'll pay market price plus twenty percent.
سأدفع سعر السوق بالإضافة إلى عشرين بالمائة.
I'll take the loss.
سأتقبل الخسارة.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
You're putting on quite an act.
أنت تمثل دوراً رائعاً.
Don't you need money?
ألا تحتاج إلى المال؟
Another twenty percent.
عشرون بالمئة أخرى.
How about it?
ما رأيك؟
Granny Chang left the house to me.
تركت لي الجدة تشانغ المنزل.
If I need money, I'll earn it myself.
إذا احتجت إلى المال، فسأكسبه بنفسي.
Earn it yourself?
هل تكسبها بنفسك؟
By doing...
بفعل...
manual labor?
العمل اليدوي؟
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
I'll hire you.
سأوظفك.
To tutor me.
لتدريسي.
Tutor you in what?
ما الذي سأدرسه لك؟
Boxing.
ملاكمة.
Boxing?
ملاكمة؟
I don't know how.
لا أعرف كيف.
Find someone else.
ابحث عن شخص آخر.
Aren't you the top student?
أليس أنت الطالب المتفوق؟
I'll hire you for two hours a day.
سأوظفك لمدة ساعتين يومياً.
Five hundred an hour.
خمسمائة في الساعة.
That's a thousand a day.
هذا يعني ألفاً في اليوم.
Ten thousand in ten days.
عشرة آلاف في عشرة أيام.
Twenty days...
عشرون يوماً...
You do the math.
قم بإجراء الحسابات بنفسك.
[TN: This is all incredibly Fake looking money. Bank of Huag???]
[ملاحظة المترجم: هذه كلها أموال مزيفة بشكل لا يصدق. بنك هواغ؟؟؟]
Why me?
لماذا أنا؟
I just want to see...
أريد فقط أن أرى...
what you're willing to do...
ما أنت على استعداد لفعله...
for money.
من أجل المال.
Just as a sparring partner?
كشريك تدريب فقط؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
You'll serve me tea and water,
ستقدم لي الشاي والماء،
run errands,
القيام بالمهام،
and be at my beck and call.
وأن تكون تحت إمرتي.
To put it bluntly,
بصراحة تامة،
you'll be my gofer.
ستكون مساعدي.
You need money, don't you?
أنت بحاجة إلى المال، أليس كذلك؟
You can steal a house,
يمكنك سرقة منزل،
you can haul bricks.
يمكنك نقل الطوب.
What's being a gofer compared to that?
ما قيمة العمل كمساعد بسيط مقارنة بذلك؟
Deal.
اتفاق.
When do we start?
متى نبدأ؟
Today.
اليوم.
Go to my house and wait for me.
اذهب إلى منزلي وانتظرني.
Come in.
ادخل.
Leave your shoes outside.
اترك حذائك بالخارج.
Don't get my house dirty.
لا تُوسّخ منزلي.
Do you know how long I made you stand there?
هل تعلم كم من الوقت جعلتك تقف هناك؟
Ten minutes.
عشر دقائق.
Feeling wronged?
هل تشعر بالظلم؟
It's your money, anyway.
إنها أموالك على أي حال.
Five hundred an hour.
خمسمائة في الساعة.
What do I have to feel wronged about?
ما الذي يجب أن أشعر بالظلم حياله؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
Let's get the rules straight first.
دعونا نوضح القواعد أولاً.
First.
أولاً.
When you're here,
عندما تكون هنا،
you have to call me Master Zhan.
يجب أن تناديني السيد زان.
What?
ماذا؟
Cat got your tongue?
هل ابتلعت القطة لسانك؟
Master Zhan.
المعلم زان.
Second.
ثانية.
When I ask you a question, you answer.
عندما أسألك سؤالاً، تجيب عليه.
You must use 'Yes'
يجب عليك استخدام "نعم".
or 'Understood.'
أو "مفهوم".
And add 'Master Zhan' at the end.
وأضف "السيد زان" في النهاية.
Is that clear?
هل هذا واضح؟
Understood.
مفهوم.
Master Zhan.
المعلم زان.
What are you smiling at?
ما الذي يجعلك تبتسم؟
I'm not smiling.
أنا لا أبتسم.
Master.
يتقن.
Third.
ثالث.
Go get me a cup of coffee.
أحضر لي فنجان قهوة.
No sugar, no milk.
بدون سكر، بدون حليب.
The temperature must be 75 degrees.
يجب أن تكون درجة الحرارة 75 درجة.
There's a thermometer in the kitchen.
يوجد مقياس حرارة في المطبخ.
Fine.
بخير.
Too bitter.
مرارة شديدة.
Wipe it up.
امسحها.
In her last year,
في عامها الأخير،
is this how you served my grandma?
هل هكذا قدمتم الخدمة لجدتي؟
No.
لا.
Granny Chang never made things difficult for me.
لم تجعل الجدة تشانغ الأمور صعبة عليّ أبداً.
Time to practice.
حان وقت التدريب.
Catch.
يمسك.
Put them on.
ارتديهما.
The rules are simple.
القواعد بسيطة.
I punch, you block.
أنا أوجّه اللكمة، وأنت تصدّها.
No dodging.
ممنوع التهرب.
You have to take the hit.
عليك أن تتحمل العواقب.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Add 'Master Zhan' at the end.
أضف "السيد زان" في النهاية.
Understood, Master Zhan.
مفهوم يا سيد زان.
Put them on properly.
ارتديها بشكل صحيح.
Don't blame me if you get a concussion.
لا تلومني إذا أصبت بارتجاج في المخ.
Where's my family's osmanthus tree?
أين شجرة الأوسمانثوس الخاصة بعائلتي؟
A typhoon knocked it down last year.
أسقطه إعصار العام الماضي.
What about the grape trellis in the yard?
ماذا عن تعريشة العنب في الفناء؟
It was taken down.
تمت إزالته.
My mom said it attracted snakes.
قالت أمي إنها تجذب الثعابين.
What about the orange cat?
وماذا عن القطة البرتقالية؟
Three months after Grandma passed away,
بعد ثلاثة أشهر من وفاة جدتي،
it died.
مات.
You seem to know everything.
يبدو أنك تعرف كل شيء.
I lived here for seven whole years.
عشت هنا لمدة سبع سنوات كاملة.
And you were gone for seven years.
وغبت لمدة سبع سنوات.
Shut up.
اسكت.
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
Get up.
استيقظ.
Let's continue.
لنكمل.
Here's today's pay.
هذا هو راتبي اليوم.
What time tomorrow?
متى غداً؟
Depends on my mood.
يعتمد ذلك على مزاجي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Jinx.
نحس.
Carry my bag for a bit.
احمل حقيبتي قليلاً.
I'll pay you.
سأدفع لك.
Manual labor counts too.
العمل اليدوي له أهمية أيضاً.
Why are you so tired?
لماذا أنت متعب جداً؟
Hurry up.
أسرع.
The Jinx is carrying his bag? What's going on?
هل يحمل جينكس حقيبته؟ ما الذي يحدث؟
A brick.
طوبة.
Three of them!
ثلاثة منهم!
Jinx.
نحس.
Finish all of this.
أنهِ كل هذا.
Why?
لماذا؟
I'm paying you.
أنا أدفع لك.
You should throw in some extra services, right?
يجب أن تقدم بعض الخدمات الإضافية، أليس كذلك؟
Which chapter?
أي فصل؟
All of it.
كل ذلك.
The entire workbook.
كتاب التمارين بأكمله.
Let's go eat.
هيا بنا نأكل.
What do you want to eat?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I want fish balls.
أريد كرات السمك.
Come on, let's go together.
هيا بنا، لنذهب معاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Aren't you going to eat?
ألن تأكل؟
Stop writing.
توقف عن الكتابة.
If you're being bullied, you have to fight back.
إذا كنت تتعرض للتنمر، فعليك أن ترد الصاع صاعين.
Cowering like that... What kind of man are you?
وأنت ترتجف هكذا... أي نوع من الرجال أنت؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Bian Ye.
بيان يي.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Bullying a classmate in broad daylight.
التنمر على زميل في الصف في وضح النهار.
This is what you get.
هذا ما ستحصل عليه.
Who the hell are you?
من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
Take this!
خذ هذا!
Zhan Wang!
زان وانغ!
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
It's not him! Stop fighting!
ليس هو! توقفوا عن الشجار!
It's not him!
ليس هو!
Stop fighting!
توقفوا عن القتال!
What are you all doing?
ماذا تفعلون جميعاً؟
Zhan Wang, stop fighting!
زان وانغ، توقف عن القتال!
Bian Ye! Zhan Wang!
بيان يي! زان وانغ!
Come out.
يخرج.
Teacher.
مدرس.
This redhead was bullying a student.
كانت هذه الفتاة ذات الشعر الأحمر تتنمر على طالبة.
He didn't bring lunch.
لم يحضر الغداء.
His mom asked me to bring him some food.
طلبت مني والدته أن أحضر له بعض الطعام.
This guy just came up and started hitting me.
هذا الرجل اقترب مني وبدأ بضربي.
What exactly happened?
ما الذي حدث بالضبط؟
Xu Yuan, speak.
شو يوان، تكلم.
Teacher.
مدرس.
My mom asked Bian Ye to bring me lunch.
طلبت أمي من بيان يي أن يحضر لي الغداء.
Zhan Wang misunderstood.
أساء زان وانغ فهم الأمر.
Bian Ye wasn't bullying me.
لم يكن بيان يي يتنمر عليّ.
That black stuff...
ذلك الشيء الأسود...
is rice?
هل الأرز هو؟
What are you looking at?
ما الذي تنظر إليه؟
I'm looking at you. Got a problem?
أنا أنظر إليك. هل لديك مشكلة؟
Are you stupid?
هل أنت غبي؟
Got a problem? Let's go after school.
هل لديك مشكلة؟ لنذهب بعد المدرسة.
Bring it on. Let's go.
هيا بنا. لننطلق.
- See you at the warehouse dock after school. - Still fighting?
- أراك في رصيف المستودع بعد المدرسة. - هل ما زلت تتشاجر؟
Are you still going to argue?
هل ستستمر في الجدال؟
It's only the second day of school.
إنه اليوم الثاني فقط من الدراسة.
Fighting on the second day.
القتال مستمر في اليوم الثاني.
Bian Ye.
بيان يي.
You're a senior now.
أنت الآن في السنة الأخيرة من الدراسة.
You've already been held back for two years.
لقد تأخرت بالفعل لمدة عامين.
You skip class every day.
أنت تتغيب عن الحصص الدراسية كل يوم.
And when you do show up, you cause trouble.
وعندما تظهر، فإنك تسبب المشاكل.
If you keep hanging out with those thugs...
إذا استمريت في التسكع مع هؤلاء البلطجية...
you're finished.
لقد انتهيت.
Teacher.
مدرس.
My family needs money.
تحتاج عائلتي إلى المال.
How else am I supposed to get by?
كيف لي أن أتدبر أموري بطريقة أخرى؟
Are you going to give it to me?
هل ستعطيني إياه؟
Also, Teacher...
أيضًا، أيها المعلم...
We were both fighting.
كنا نتشاجر كلانا.
Don't play favorites.
لا تُحابِ أحداً.
He threw the first punch.
لقد وجّه اللكمة الأولى.
Is it because he's some young master from Jingzhou?
هل السبب أنه سيد شاب من جينغتشو؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Zhan Wang.
زان وانغ.
Teacher.
مدرس.
I don't think he's feeling well.
لا أعتقد أنه يشعر بأنه على ما يرام.
I'll take him to the nurse's office.
سآخذه إلى عيادة الممرضة.
Okay.
تمام.
Wimp.
جبان.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Two.
اثنين.
How could I have such a disgusting son?
كيف لي أن أرزق بابن مقرف كهذا؟
Do you know what you did wrong?
هل تعرف ما الخطأ الذي ارتكبته؟
I did nothing wrong.
لم أفعل شيئاً خاطئاً.
How are you feeling?
كيف تشعر؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I came back to Hongzhen a while ago.
لقد عدت إلى هونغ تشن منذ فترة.
Now...
الآن...
I'm working part-time as the school nurse.
أعمل بدوام جزئي كممرضة مدرسية.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
How are you feeling?
كيف تشعر؟
Dizzy.
دائِخ.
Nauseous.
غثيان.
Blurry vision.
رؤية ضبابية.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
It's just low blood sugar.
إنه مجرد انخفاض في نسبة السكر في الدم.
Low blood sugar wouldn't cause this kind of...
انخفاض نسبة السكر في الدم لا يسبب هذا النوع من...
sudden, temporary loss of consciousness...
فقدان الوعي المفاجئ والمؤقت ...
accompanied by stiff limbs.
مصحوبة بتيبس في الأطراف.
Xiao Wang.
شياو وانغ.
What's really wrong with you?
ما الذي تعاني منه حقاً؟
Tell your brother.
أخبر أخاك.
Brother.
أخ.
You're not my brother.
أنت لست أخي.
The Zhan family has no one like you.
عائلة زان ليس لديها أحد مثلك.
I have to get to class.
يجب أن أذهب إلى الصف.
I'm the school nurse here.
أنا ممرضة المدرسة هنا.
You can't leave in your condition.
لا يمكنك المغادرة وأنت على هذه الحال.
Besides...
بجانب...
I'm also your guardian.
أنا أيضاً ولي أمرك.
Guardian?
حارس؟
Someone who was kicked out of the house...
شخص طُرد من المنزل...
and disowned by the family?
وهل تبرأ منه أفراد العائلة؟
Even if I was kicked out...
حتى لو طُردت...
I'm still your brother.
ما زلت أخاك.
Zhan Wang.
زان وانغ.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine now.
أنا بخير الآن.
Xu Yuan.
شو يوان.
Get me out of here.
أخرجوني من هنا.
Xiao Wang.
شياو وانغ.
Hurry.
عجل.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
When you're around me...
عندما تكون بجانبي...
It has nothing to do with you.
الأمر لا علاقة لك به.
It was me.
كنت أنا.
I just couldn't stand that redhead.
لم أستطع تحمل تلك الشقراء.
That workbook...
ذلك الكتاب التدريبي...
give it back to me.
أعده إليّ.
You don't have to do it anymore.
لم يعد عليك فعل ذلك.
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
I'll give it back this afternoon.
سأعيدها بعد ظهر اليوم.
That's not what I meant.
لم يكن هذا ما قصدته.
He's so handsome.
إنه وسيم للغاية.
So handsome.
وسيم جداً.
Even his warm-ups are handsome.
حتى ملابس الإحماء الخاصة به أنيقة.
Xu Yuan.
شو يوان.
Is it because you don't exercise...
هل السبب هو عدم ممارستك للرياضة؟
that you're this out of breath from carrying my bag?
هل يعقل أنك تلهث هكذا من حمل حقيبتي؟
I go for a run by the sea every night.
أذهب للركض على شاطئ البحر كل ليلة.
Exercising alone is so boring.
ممارسة الرياضة بمفردك أمر ممل للغاية.
You need to be part of a group.
يجب أن تكون جزءًا من مجموعة.
How about this? I'll take you to play ball.
ما رأيك بهذا؟ سآخذك للعب الكرة.
Zhan Wang.
زان وانغ.
Can you stop messing around?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن العبث؟
All these girls are here to watch you play.
جميع هؤلاء الفتيات هنا لمشاهدتك وأنت تلعب.
If you bring him along...
إذا أحضرته معك...
who would want to see the guy they like...
من سيرغب برؤية الشخص الذي يعجبه...
get hurt because of him?
هل ستتأذى بسببه؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You guys go ahead and play.
هيا يا رفاق، العبوا.
I'm not very good at it.
أنا لستُ بارعاً في ذلك.
Stop, Zhan Wang.
توقف يا زان وانغ.
Stop.
قف.
Zhan Wang.
زان وانغ.
I've had enough.
لقد طفح الكيل.
I've really had enough.
لقد طفح الكيل حقاً.
I don't care if you...
لا يهمني إن كنت...
genuinely want to be my friend...
أرغب حقًا في أن أكون صديقي...
or if you just think it's fun to mess with me.
أو إذا كنت تعتقد فقط أن من الممتع أن تعبث معي.
Let's just end it here.
لننهِ الأمر هنا.
Stay away from me.
ابتعد عني.
It's better for everyone.
إنه أفضل للجميع.
That's not what I meant.
لم يكن هذا ما قصدته.
Watch out!
انتبه!
See?
يرى؟
It happened again.
لقد حدث ذلك مرة أخرى.
I always...
أنا دائماً...
end up dragging down the people around me.
ينتهي بي الأمر بسحب الناس من حولي إلى الأسفل.
Xu Yuan.
شو يوان.
Don't you dare say that.
إياك أن تقول ذلك.
I, Zhan Wang, don't believe in any of that jinx nonsense.
أنا، زان وانغ، لا أؤمن بأي من هذا الهراء المتعلق بالنحس.
You're the one who just saved me.
أنت من أنقذني للتو.
Your hand is hurt.
يدك مصابة.
Let's go to the nurse's office.
هيا بنا إلى عيادة الممرضة.
It's fine. I'll take care of it at home.
لا بأس. سأعتني بالأمر في المنزل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Student Zhan Wang.
الطالب زان وانغ.
We meet again.
نلتقي مجدداً.
At this rate...
وبهذا المعدل...
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Was it a fight this time?
هل كانت معركة هذه المرة؟
Or...
أو...
an accident?
حادث؟
He scraped his hand.
خدش يده.
Take care of it.
اعتني بالأمر.
Here, let me see.
دعني أرى.
It's a scrape.
إنها مجرد خدشة.
Bleeding a little.
ينزف قليلاً.
It just needs to be cleaned and disinfected.
كل ما يحتاجه هو التنظيف والتعقيم.
You two are inseparable, aren't you?
أنتما لا تنفصلان، أليس كذلك؟
Mind your own business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
I have to take a call.
عليّ أن أرد على مكالمة.
You.
أنت.
Just clean it for him.
نظفها له فقط.
The iodine and cotton swabs are here.
اليود والمسحات القطنية موجودة هنا.
Me?
أنا؟
Your mess.
فوضاك.
You clean it up.
قم بتنظيفه.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Xu Yuan can tell you what to do.
بإمكان شو يوان أن يخبرك بما يجب عليك فعله.
He's practically my apprentice.
هو عملياً تلميذي.
He's doing this on purpose.
إنه يفعل ذلك عن قصد.
Dr. Zhan.
د. زان.
You two know each other?
هل تعرفان بعضكما؟
Sort of.
نوعاً ما.
He's my older brother.
هو أخي الأكبر.
Sort of?
نوعاً ما؟
Tell me if it hurts.
أخبرني إن كان الأمر مؤلماً.
Idiot.
غبي.
Did you have to jump in front of me?
هل كان عليك أن تقفز أمامي؟
And you got yourself hurt.
وقد تسببت في إصابة نفسك.
Your head is more important.
عقلك أهم.
My head...
رأسي...
what's it to you?
وما شأنك أنت؟
Because...
لأن...
I'm a jinx.
أنا نذير شؤم.
Nonsense.
هراء.
I don't believe that.
لا أصدق ذلك.
Xu Yuan.
شو يوان.
You say you're a jinx...
تقول إنك نذير شؤم...
but does that jinx work on yourself too?
لكن هل ينطبق هذا النحس عليك أنت أيضاً؟
Why is it that after I showed up...
لماذا بعد أن حضرت...
you started having bad luck too?
هل بدأت تواجه سوء الحظ أيضاً؟
I wish it were only me.
أتمنى لو كنت أنا فقط.
Is it wrapped up?
هل تم تغليفها؟
If it is, let's go to class.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فلنذهب إلى الفصل.
Let's go see a movie later.
لنذهب لمشاهدة فيلم لاحقاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Yeah, sure. Let's go.
أجل، بالتأكيد. هيا بنا.
Let me tell you...
دعني أخبرك...
that movie is awesome.
هذا الفيلم رائع.
That kid, Zhan Wang...
ذلك الطفل، زان وانغ...
chickened out.
تراجعت.
Waiting for Zhan Wang?
هل تنتظرون زان وانغ؟
None of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Does the school nurse manage student fights now?
هل تتولى ممرضة المدرسة الآن إدارة شجارات الطلاب؟
Just a suggestion.
مجرد اقتراح.
I suggest...
أقترح...
you stop bothering him.
توقف عن إزعاجه.
Says who?
من قال ذلك؟
What gives you the right to tell me what to do?
ما الذي يمنحك الحق في أن تخبرني بما يجب علي فعله؟
That kid's not here again. Let's go.
هذا الطفل ليس هنا مجدداً. هيا بنا.
You know him?
هل تعرفه؟
You're so nosy.
أنت فضولي للغاية.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Right on time.
في الموعد المحدد تماماً.
Let's make this quick. Saves us the trouble.
لنُسرع في هذا الأمر. هذا يوفر علينا المتاعب.
Bian Ye.
بيان يي.
Finally found you.
وأخيرًا وجدتك.
The score from last time...
النتيجة من المرة الماضية...
it's time to settle it.
حان وقت حسم الأمر.
Brother Hua.
الأخ هوا.
I swear I'll pay you back next month.
أقسم أنني سأسدد لك المبلغ الشهر القادم.
Next month?
الشهر المقبل؟
I want it now.
أريده الآن.
This has nothing to do with you.
هذا لا علاقة لك به.
You should go.
يجب أن تذهب.
We'll deal with our stuff later.
سنتعامل مع أغراضنا لاحقاً.
Let's take them out first.
لنقم بإخراجهم أولاً.
My hands were getting itchy anyway.
كانت يداي تشعران بالحكة على أي حال.
You're asking for it.
أنت من تطلب ذلك.
Run!
يجري!
Split up!
انفصلوا!
After them!
بعدهم!
This way.
من هنا.
They went this way.
لقد سلكوا هذا الطريق.
Check over there.
تحقق من هناك.
Over here.
هنا.
Hurry!
عجل!
Where'd they go?
أين ذهبوا؟
It's a dead end.
إنه طريق مسدود.
Let's look over there.
لنلقِ نظرة هناك.
Okay, sure.
حسناً، بالتأكيد.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Helping Uncle Wang mend some nets.
مساعدة العم وانغ في إصلاح بعض الشباك.
To earn some extra cash.
لكسب بعض المال الإضافي.
They went east.
اتجهوا شرقاً.
But they'll be back.
لكنهم سيعودون.
You should wait a bit.
يجب أن تنتظر قليلاً.
If you go out now, they'll see you.
إذا خرجت الآن، فسوف يرونك.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
You know this place well.
أنت تعرف هذا المكان جيداً.
I grew up on this dock.
لقد نشأت على هذا الرصيف.
This part of the dock...
هذا الجزء من الرصيف...
used to be where my grandma and I played hide-and-seek.
كان هذا المكان الذي اعتدت أن ألعب فيه أنا وجدتي لعبة الغميضة.
About what happened at school today...
بخصوص ما حدث في المدرسة اليوم...
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It was a big misunderstanding.
كان ذلك سوء فهم كبير.
I shouldn't have...
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أفعل ذلك...
jumped in without knowing the facts.
اندفعوا دون معرفة الحقائق.
It's just that kid...
إنه ذلك الطفل فقط...
he doesn't look like a delivery boy.
لا يبدو كعامل توصيل.
My mom's busy at the noodle shop.
أمي مشغولة في محل المعكرونة.
She doesn't have time to run errands.
ليس لديها وقت للقيام بالمهام.
Bian Ye helps out at our place.
يساعد بيان يي في منزلنا.
He needs the money.
إنه بحاجة إلى المال.
And we need cheap labor.
ونحن بحاجة إلى عمالة رخيصة.
So my mom always has him deliver lunch to me and Xu Nuo.
لذلك، تطلب أمي منه دائماً أن يوصل لي ولـ Xu Nuo الغداء.
Bian Ye does have a bit of a temper.
بيان يي لديه بعض المزاج الحاد.
He's always grumbling when he delivers the food.
إنه دائماً ما يتذمر عندما يقوم بتوصيل الطعام.
But he always shows up.
لكنه دائماً ما يظهر.
Why did you...
لماذا فعلت ذلك...
insist on fighting Bian Ye?
هل تصر على قتال بيان يي؟
He rubbed me the wrong way.
لقد أثار غضبي.
But you never get involved in other people's business at school.
لكن لا تتدخل أبدًا في شؤون الآخرين في المدرسة.
I thought he was giving you trouble.
ظننت أنه كان يسبب لك المتاعب.
I can't stand seeing people get bullied.
لا أطيق رؤية الناس يتعرضون للتنمر.
You've got a tear.
لقد ذرفت دمعة.
I do?
أفعل؟
Must have snagged it on something.
لا بد أنه علق بشيء ما.
Lift it up.
ارفعها.
There.
هناك.
It should be clear now.
ينبغي أن يكون الأمر واضحاً الآن.
We should go.
يجب أن نذهب.
Stay close to me.
ابقَ قريباً مني.
Don't make a sound.
لا تُصدر صوتاً.
This path...
هذا المسار...
you know it surprisingly well.
أنت تعرف ذلك جيداً بشكل مدهش.
I didn't have any friends when I was little.
لم يكن لدي أي أصدقاء عندما كنت صغيراً.
So I walked every one of these alleys by myself.
لذلك تجولت في كل هذه الأزقة بمفردي.
That way leads to the back street.
هذا الطريق يؤدي إلى الشارع الخلفي.
Your villa is in that direction.
تقع الفيلا الخاصة بك في ذلك الاتجاه.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Me?
أنا؟
I'm going back to the warehouse.
سأعود إلى المستودع.
I haven't finished mending the fishing nets.
لم أنتهِ من إصلاح شباك الصيد.
Are you that desperate for money?
هل أنت في حاجة ماسة للمال إلى هذه الدرجة؟
I still haven't saved up enough.
لم أدخر ما يكفي بعد.
Tomorrow...
غداً...
are we still on for tutoring?
هل ما زلنا ملتزمين بجلسات التدريس؟
We are.
نحن.
Okay.
تمام.
Xu Yuan.
شو يوان.
Today...
اليوم...
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You helped me first.
لقد ساعدتني أولاً.
Even though it was a mistake.
على الرغم من أنه كان خطأً.
Bian Ye.
بيان يي.
If I don't break one of your legs today...
إذا لم أكسر إحدى ساقيك اليوم...
I'll take your last name.
سآخذ اسم عائلتك.
Bian the dog.
بيان الكلب.
That's not much of a last name anyway.
هذا ليس لقبًا مميزًا على أي حال.
Who are you calling a dog?
من الذي تصفه بالكلب؟
Stop!
قف!
How much does he owe?
كم يبلغ المبلغ الذي يدين به؟
What?
ماذا؟
I said...
قلت...
how much money does he owe you?
كم من المال يدين لك؟
His debt...
دينه...
I'll clear it.
سأقوم بتنظيفه.
Can we go now?
هل يمكننا الذهاب الآن؟
Found yourself a sugar mama already?
هل وجدتَ بالفعل امرأة ثرية تكبرك سناً؟
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Yeah, your mom.
نعم، والدتك.
Let go of me.
اتركني وشأني.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Don't forget...
لا تنسى...
I'm your creditor now.
أنا دائنك الآن.
Let go of me.
اتركني وشأني.
Are you calm now?
هل أنت هادئ الآن؟
I'm not selling my body.
أنا لا أبيع جسدي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm not into kids.
أنا لا أحب الأطفال.
Then what do you want?
إذن ماذا تريد؟
Do doctors run a loan shark business on the side?
هل يمارس الأطباء أعمال الإقراض الربوي في أوقات فراغهم؟
Starting tomorrow...
ابتداءً من الغد...
you'll come to my place for two hours of tutoring every afternoon.
ستأتي إلى منزلي لمدة ساعتين من الدروس الخصوصية كل عصر.
To pay off your debt.
لسداد ديونك.
Tutoring?
هل تبحث عن دروس خصوصية؟
Do I look like the studying type to you?
هل أبدو لك من النوع الذي يحب الدراسة؟
Whether you look like it or not...
سواء بدا ذلك واضحاً أم لا...
we'll find out when we try.
سنعرف ذلك عندما نحاول.
Can you walk?
هل تستطيع المشي؟
My hand...
يدي...
it hurts a little.
يؤلمني قليلاً.
Tough it out.
تحمّل الأمر.
So now you feel the pain.
والآن تشعر بالألم.
You weren't so scared when you were fighting, were you?
لم تكن خائفاً جداً عندما كنت تقاتل، أليس كذلك؟
Who said I was scared?
من قال إني خائف؟
It's fine. It's just a small cut.
لا بأس. إنه مجرد جرح صغير.
If you don't treat a small wound properly...
إذا لم تعالج جرحاً صغيراً بشكل صحيح...
it can get seriously infected.
قد يُصاب بعدوى خطيرة.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I think I pulled a muscle in my back.
أعتقد أنني أصبت بتمزق عضلي في ظهري.
Let me give you some acupuncture.
دعني أقدم لك بعض العلاج بالإبر الصينية.
No, thanks.
ًلا شكرا.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
I'm a doctor.
أنا طبيب.
How does it feel now?
كيف تشعر الآن؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Tomorrow at 5 p.m.
غداً الساعة الخامسة مساءً
Come to my place.
تعال إلى منزلي.
I'll tutor you.
سأقوم بتدريسك.
I said I don't want to.
قلتُ إنني لا أريد ذلك.
You don't have a choice.
ليس لديك خيار.
Don't forget...
لا تنسى...
I'm your creditor.
أنا دائنك.
I'll earn the money to pay you back.
سأجمع المال لأرد لك الجميل.
Perhaps...
ربما...
you'd prefer I go to your school gate...
تفضل أن أذهب إلى بوابة مدرستك...
to pick you up after class?
هل يمكنني أن آتي لأخذك بعد انتهاء الحصة؟
You're insane.
أنت مجنون.
You'll have to pull down your pants a bit.
سيتعين عليك إنزال سروالك قليلاً.
I need to needle your Huantiao acupoint.
أحتاج إلى وخز نقطة هوانتياو لديك بالإبرة.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
I'm a doctor.
أنا طبيب.
Bian Ye is fine.
بيان يي بخير.
I paid off his debt.
لقد سددت دينه.
Take care of yourself.
اعتنِ بنفسك.
Let me know if you feel anything unusual.
أخبرني إذا شعرت بأي شيء غير عادي.
Since you're here, you should study hard.
بما أنك هنا، فعليك أن تدرس بجد.
That kid today seemed like a decent guy.
بدا ذلك الطفل اليوم وكأنه شخص جيد.
Worth being friends with.
يستحق أن تكون صديقاً له.
Stay away from me.
ابتعد عني.
It's better for everyone.
إنه أفضل للجميع.
Watch out.
انتبه.
This path...
هذا المسار...
you know it surprisingly well.
أنت تعرف ذلك جيداً بشكل مدهش.
I didn't have any friends when I was little.
لم يكن لدي أي أصدقاء عندما كنت صغيراً.
So I walked every one of these alleys by myself.
لذلك تجولت في كل هذه الأزقة بمفردي.
Today...
اليوم...
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You helped me first.
لقد ساعدتني أولاً.
Even though it was a mistake.
على الرغم من أنه كان خطأً.
Xu Yuan.
شو يوان.
What kind of person are you, really?
ما نوع الشخص الذي أنت عليه حقاً؟
Mom.
أم.
Why are you so late?
لماذا تأخرت كل هذا الوقت؟
A classmate needed me for something.
كان أحد زملائي في الصف بحاجة إليّ لأمر ما.
Look at the state you're in.
انظر إلى حالتك.
Mom.
أم.
Um...
واحد...
Is the paper box Granny Chang left still here?
هل ما زال صندوق الورق الذي تركته الجدة تشانغ موجوداً هنا؟
Yes, it is.
نعم إنه كذلك.
It's under your bed. I haven't touched it.
إنه تحت سريرك. لم ألمسه.
Why?
لماذا؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Mom, you should get some rest.
يا أمي، يجب أن تستريحي قليلاً.